

Ho Thi Diem

Front-end Developer

Date of birth: December 21, 1997

Gender: Female

Phone: 0708005636

Email: diemho2112@gmail.com

Address: K249/68 Ha Huy Tap, Thanh Khe, Da Nang, Vietnam

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/diem-ho-222816180

OBJECTIVE

As an innovative front-end developer with the experience of 1 year, I am willing to interact with new tools, learn new skills and make full use of my creativity in order to build customized websites with the best user experience as well as efficiency. Therefore, I would like to join your company to achieve the following goals:

- Take advantages of skills & experiences about developing software
- Have a chance of learning a lot from seniors and projects in the company
- Contribute to the development of the company
- Have a chance of indulging my passion toward Information Technology

EDUCATION

Oct 2015 - May 2019	Troy University American Degree Program at Duy Tan university Major: Corporate Administration
Oct 2012 - May 2015	Nguyen Binh Khiem high school for the gifted Major: English

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2018 - Present English Ocean Center

Teaching Assistant
Main responsibilities:

- Grading and evaluating students performance
- Provide support for students during lecture and practicing work
- Prepare lecture

Nov 2018 - Jun 2019 Lean Start Lab

Full Stack Developer Internship

Lean Start Lab is a technology development agency that help startups

create, build, and launch products.

Main responsibilities:

- Experience with developing user friendly front-end web application

using ReactJS

- Develop and build API for web and mobile application using

Laravel Framework

June 2019 - Nov 2019 Lean Start Lab

Front-end Developer

Main responsibilities:

- Build the web application using the combination of html, sass and Laravel Framework
- Research new tools, build and optimize reusable module list for frontend web application using ReactJs
- Build a small front-end web application using Angular

CERTIFICATIONS

2016	IELTS Band 5.5
2018	Complete the training course Agile Project Management with Scrum

SKILLS

Front End	html, css, sass, ReactJs, Angular
Back End	Php, Laravel Framework

INTERESTS

- Traveling to explore new places and cultures
- Watching films to improve the culture in myself
- Watching volleyball matches
- Going for a walk and a talk with my close friends

STRENGTHS

- Self-study, enthusiasm and responsibility in working
- Have studied in English environment during the period of time at the university
- Working under high pressure and meeting the tight deadline
- Be easily adaptable to new tools and programing languages